<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Phil 355]]></title>
  <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil355/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil355/"/>
  <updated>2013-09-03T12:16:55-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://apc.github.io/phil355/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alejandro Pérez Carballo]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readings for Thursday]]></title>
    <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil355/blog/2013/09/03/readings-for-thursday/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-03T12:13:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://apc.github.io/phil355/blog/2013/09/03/readings-for-thursday</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The readings for Thursday&rsquo;s class are now available in electronic form on <a href="./readings">the readings page</a>. Starting next week, I will assume you each have access to the required books for this class.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
    <link href="http://apc.github.io/phil355/blog/2013/08/19/welcome/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-19T14:45:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://apc.github.io/phil355/blog/2013/08/19/welcome</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the website for PHIL 355 at <a href="http://www.umass.edu">UMass Amherst</a>. Announcements, readings, and other relevant information will be posted here. If you are enrolled in this class, you should be checking <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil355">this website</a> regularly, as well as the <a href="http://perezcarballo.org/phil355/calendar">course calendar</a>.</p>

<p>For your convenience, I have set up a mailing list for this course. I encourage you to subscribe in order to be notified of announcements on this site. Note, however, that you will only be notified of updates to the site once a day. (If there are no new updates on a given day, you will receive no emails.)</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>I have also set up a <a href="">Moodle page</a> for this website. However, we will only use that page for two purposes: you will submit your assignments there, and you will be able to review your grades for the course. If I ever need you to check the <a href="">Moodle page</a> I will make sure to make an announcement <a href="">on this page</a>.</p>

<p>If you are enrolled in this class, or are thinking about enrolling, you may want to take a look at the <a href="">course syllabus</a>. (N.B.: I will not distribute paper copies on the first day of class.)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
